<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>java on Ace The Cloud Skills</title><link>https://acethecloud.com/tags/java/</link><description>Recent content in java on Ace The Cloud Skills</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:38:27 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://acethecloud.com/tags/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Comprehensive Guide to Workflow as a Service System Design</title><link>https://acethecloud.com/blog/a-comprehensive-guide-to-workflow-system-design/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:38:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://acethecloud.com/blog/a-comprehensive-guide-to-workflow-system-design/</guid><description>Alright, let&amp;rsquo;s design a Workflow as a Service (WaaS) system. Designing a system like this is a broad topic, and a detailed design could span many pages. Here&amp;rsquo;s a high-level overview to get you started.
1. Overview: Workflow as a Service (WaaS) is a cloud-based solution that allows businesses to create, manage, and optimize workflows without the need for on-premises infrastructure. It provides a way to automate repetitive tasks and processes, ensuring they are executed consistently.</description></item><item><title>10 mistakes those should be avoided in GoLang</title><link>https://acethecloud.com/blog/10-mistakes-those-should-be-avoided-in-golang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:38:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://acethecloud.com/blog/10-mistakes-those-should-be-avoided-in-golang/</guid><description>Go is a statically typed, concurrent, garbage-collected programming language developed at Google. It has gained popularity in recent years due to its simplicity, performance, and strong support for concurrency. Despite its simplicity, there are still some common mistakes that developers make when writing Go code. Here are the top 10 bad mistakes to be avoided in Go, along with code examples for each of them:
Not checking for errors Go functions often return multiple values, with the second value being an error.</description></item><item><title>9 Features of Spring Cloud</title><link>https://acethecloud.com/blog/9-features-of-spring-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:38:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://acethecloud.com/blog/9-features-of-spring-cloud/</guid><description>Spring Cloud is a framework for building microservices-based applications on the Spring platform. It provides tools and services for distributed systems, including service registration and discovery, routing, load balancing, circuit breakers, and more. In this blog post, we’ll cover these features in depth, including code examples in Java for each of them.
Distributed/versioned configuration Service registration and discovery Routing Service-to-service calls Load balancing Circuit Breakers Global locks Leadership election and cluster state Distributed messaging 1.</description></item><item><title>The Kubernetes Handbook: A Comprehensive guide of 100 Q&amp;A</title><link>https://acethecloud.com/blog/100-java-programming-and-lld-interview-questions-handbook-with-answers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:38:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://acethecloud.com/blog/100-java-programming-and-lld-interview-questions-handbook-with-answers/</guid><description>Here are 100 Java Programming and LLD Interview Questions Handbook with Answers: These questions cover a range of topics within Java and its ecosystem. Being able to address them would demonstrate a deep understanding of Java&amp;rsquo;s inner workings, standard libraries, design patterns, and best practices.
Describe the Java Memory Model. How does Java Garbage Collection work? Describe the major garbage collectors and their advantages/disadvantages. What are the differences between ArrayList and LinkedList?</description></item></channel></rss>